{
    "subject": "resource/The_Adventures_of_Abney_&_Teal",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Shingai_Shoniwa",
    "human_readable": "The Adventures of Abney & Teal stars Shingai Shoniwa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9674093723297119,
            "question": "What kind of character does Shingai Shoniwa play in The Adventures of Abney & Teal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273755311965942,
            "question": "Who stars in The Adventures of Abney & Teal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8139813542366028,
            "question": "What is the name of the show starring Shingai Shoniwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7516511082649231,
            "question": "Is Shingai Shoniwa an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6667616367340088,
            "question": "Name a television show featuring Shingai Shoniwa."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6110686659812927,
            "question": "Is The Adventures of Abney & Teal a popular show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5650525093078613,
            "question": "Where can I watch The Adventures of Abney & Teal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315354466438293,
            "question": "Do you know any other works by Shingai Shoniwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4750031530857086,
            "question": "What are some other shows similar to The Adventures of Abney & Teal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4747568666934967,
            "question": "What genre is The Adventures of Abney & Teal likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Adventures of Abney & Teal stars Shingai Shoniwa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4219_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other shows similar to The Adventures of Abney & Teal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4219_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any other works by Shingai Shoniwa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4219_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch The Adventures of Abney & Teal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4219_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4219_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Teal is voiced by Shingai Shoniwa\", which implies that Shingai Shoniwa is a star of The Adventures of Abney & Teal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Shingai Shoniwa provides the voice for Teal, supporting the statement that The Adventures of Abney & Teal stars Shingai Shoniwa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}